I'd like to... we have about
half an hour until friends are leaving. We'll be
over you. If you
said 10 o'clock, you lied to me again. Okay,
9:45, 13 minutes to go to China.
I can do that without Strauss. Can I
do that? We changed three and a half chapters,
like Erich's school, but I still have
two and a half chapters. I didn't forget that,
but how do you see, you did quite well.
And slowly,
I want to show the first minute of a video.
Can you turn on the projector?
Okay, the first chapter, that we... that...
Marica from Rio and object...
there's a nice video that's on
connoisseurs.
[Music]
There's a problem with how we see things
because it's a problem with how light
gets to Earth. There's a problem.
Stephen Hawking couldn't
figure it out,
but we figured it out. So here
's the problem.
I'm not going to show the whole thing.
[Music]
Yes.
The magazine... it doesn't make sense. Still
in quantum physics,
we still don't know how
sunlight reaches Earth. Without the sun...
We would die if we had no food,
we have none at the burner
[Music]
how does that come from the sun, we don't know, how does that
come socially, and that's chapter
3, yes, and the judge, chapter 3, how does that come
from the sun, comes
and here me, and the sun should hit the earth, how does
the light of the sun come to the earth
together with a spirit, how does
food grow from the sun, the ones that come from you,
that covers chapter 3, chapter 4,
investigation of the visitors for this, for that, something
strange for the elements,
the results of the elements, the strange thing about it
is, aspirin has a chemical inside it,
and when we
have headaches, our mother taught us,
I remember that my mother had said
aspirin, as a child I
always had bad headaches, aspirin,
once I took exactly what you did, nothing
worked,
and then I didn't, I had
n't reached my room,
I went into my brother's bed,
I took an aspirin
and nothing, nothing happened  Then
I asked Mom and called out, "
I still have a headache!"
Then I took a second one.
Ten minutes later, still with the same
headache,
I threw up my arms, "I
need another aspirin!"
And then she read on the
bottle, "For children, only two. You can't
have another one, unfortunately." And
I said, "I still have a
headache."
Then she showed very bad things. Sometimes you have to have a
headache, and then
I... and then, of course, we always...
our mother... "Okay, Mom." Sometimes, sometimes
the aspirin works, and then...
then the aspirin does
n't work. "Okay, darling," unfortunately, it's like that. It
's long until... She lied to me.
She was a bad installer in
[music].
She didn't tell me the truth.
She didn't understand. Very naked, not even in
itself... understood the chapter,
chapter 4.
She believes that she believed in two
different molecules of aspirin. She
bought the one from Berlin. It has a tip,
has a special... a
special molecule. I believed that...
hidden that... that is the second
example, the chip that...  Chapter 4,
we were really examples, what was
Chapter 3, but light,
how do we get a light on Earth?
What is Chapter 4,
Chapter 5, and the definition of
editorial work? At the celebration, it stays hot and
burns.
Nobody took hot and burns,
and that's a sign of this thing, this
sign of this thing. That's
Chapter 5, then fire,
that means it doesn't come up often. What is the
practical and practical application?
I remember that I gave that to a
court in New York because
you get a three-year loan. That was very
difficult. I taught the 18th Kruse.
That would be hard. I made an
announcement: I'm
leaving New York, and everyone was... I
remember, I'm going to leave again.
I'm going to Arizona to get fit for three
years
in the desert, and everyone was warming up. I'm going to do
another station
in the World Trade Center, and I've
given a thing since the end of the war that steel in
this building has... Lakner, it's hard.
That can hold the whole building, and
what holds that?  World Trade Center is the
steel and in this stable Markus Lakner
hard and strong right I
remember lecture that is once that
I was there it is not the lag saw it
is not the hair and that is not from
not the hard and the strong beer
that is not in the stable inside it is
not the heart and the strong steel inside
is what holds this roof are those the turning point
then came his seed thanks have the roof up there
to hold that is not the choice
they do not think so warm
if you want a roof over your head
apartment or a place
then you have to do the 13 steps
meditations for other people so that
they have places where they
can stay and then the building will not
collapse
what happened and then I went on a
three-year council
and I can remember and suddenly there were a lot of
military planes practicing
and we thought we are out here
what is going on here that is going on
before we don't know how we got out then
like the newspaper the
big newspapers are welcome it has
three pages and bands are  They came to us,
interviewed us, and the only ones
who know that they don't know that the
World Trade Center collapsed understand, understands,
yes, last time here,
I have 30 seconds left
when the Frauenkirche comes, and
if someone starts writing there,
I imagine that he's Jutta at the
table, what if you feel
stressed at home, then there's
telling at home, then you're fat, physics
stressed, last night I
ate three bowls,
I'm tired, and then I eat so that
the woman always thinks GM isn't
nice to me, I eat something so that I feel happy, make myself
happy, I don't like that, quite Utah
will make me
happy,
which part of Jutta, the part of
mine, twice the tongue, red wig,
teeth,
the front part of the tongue touches this, the
food, and that's what's achieved,
chapter 6
[Music],
that to crystals, touches medicine, can,
if they touch, then they must
go into each other, they can't touch each other like that,
if they then, until the
sugar, butter, investment, the tongue, a
little sugar, become, because the tongue had to,
on  The sugar advertises, and that's
not possible.
The tongue doesn't allow it. Then
they can't influence each other.
Understand if the sugar
can give a taste to hunger without
mixing, so that the doll would also
get the taste because they do
n't touch each other out there. The white
stuff inside would give you a good
taste.
Why do you say that happened? Because the
associated taste of
sugar was Monday, I was there. Then they ca
n't touch. If they
touch, then they have to mix. That, of
course, can lead to a certain taste. Just
like the man insulted the woman, they
have to mix somehow so
that he doesn't.
Then puberty can also give her the
taste.
I don't mix either. Just
not so much sugar mixes
with the tongue.
And then the sugar and Tokyo should
give the tongue taste, and if they mix,
then they are both. That's
sugar too. I don't know what the problem is
that it's not possible for the woman to feel
better when she is. It's not possible.
The last question:
then you have to go. She has to
make an announcement. Why?
Why does the woman feel more  It's
very pleasant if the husband
should write to her, that's why he
already ate 330 yesterday,
why how she eats it, she
relaxes, pleasant peace, if the
husband is angry then she needs
something sweet, she says, it's too much stress, so
Jutta gives him the sweet taste,
that the joker gives the 514 steps of
Tongling, the karma comes to you through the
weather, later do you need that
or not,
next time please can you, that's how
we use the five chapters, now it's
not theory used, very clever,
try it in the 13 stages of the
dome information, commitment and urge,
live,
married today, ok team